[
  {
    "question": "How many goals have occurred so far in the first half?",
    "choices": [
      "A. 0",
      "B. 1",
      "C. 2",
      "D. 3"
    ],
    "answer": "B",
    "type": "past",
    "question_level": "match",
    "related_event_index": [
      7
    ],
    "current_event_index": 7,
    "index": 0,
    "event_type": "goal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team has scored more goals in the first half up to now?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Chelsea",
      "B. Opponent",
      "C. Both teams have scored equally",
      "D. No goals yet"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "past",
    "question_level": "team",
    "related_event_index": [
      7
    ],
    "current_event_index": 7,
    "index": 1,
    "event_type": "goal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was the first player to score in the match?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Cesar Azpilicueta",
      "B. Opponent Player 1",
      "C. Opponent Player 2",
      "D. No goals yet"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "past",
    "question_level": "player",
    "related_event_index": [
      7
    ],
    "current_event_index": 7,
    "index": 2,
    "event_type": "goal"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many total goals occurred in the first half?",
    "choices": [
      "A. 0",
      "B. 1",
      "C. 2",
      "D. 3"
    ],
    "answer": "B",
    "type": "half",
    "question_level": "match",
    "related_event_index": [
      7
    ],
    "current_event_index": null,
    "index": 3,
    "event_type": "goal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team had the most goals in the first half?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Chelsea",
      "B. Opponent",
      "C. Both teams scored equally",
      "D. No goals"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "half",
    "question_level": "team",
    "related_event_index": [
      7
    ],
    "current_event_index": null,
    "index": 4,
    "event_type": "goal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who were all the players involved in first half goals?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Cesar Azpilicueta",
      "B. Opponent Player 1",
      "C. Both A and B",
      "D. No goals"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "half",
    "question_level": "player",
    "related_event_index": [
      7
    ],
    "current_event_index": null,
    "index": 5,
    "event_type": "goal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Will there be more goals in the first half?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Yes",
      "B. No"
    ],
    "answer": "B",
    "type": "future",
    "question_level": "match",
    "related_event_index": [],
    "current_event_index": 7,
    "index": 6,
    "event_type": "goal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team is more likely to get the next goal?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Chelsea",
      "B. Opponent",
      "C. Both equally",
      "D. No more goals"
    ],
    "answer": "D",
    "type": "future",
    "question_level": "team",
    "related_event_index": [],
    "current_event_index": 7,
    "index": 7,
    "event_type": "goal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which player is most likely to be involved in the next goal?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Cesar Azpilicueta",
      "B. Opponent Player 1",
      "C. Opponent Player 2",
      "D. No more goals"
    ],
    "answer": "D",
    "type": "future",
    "question_level": "player",
    "related_event_index": [],
    "current_event_index": 7,
    "index": 8,
    "event_type": "goal"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many corners have occurred so far in the first half up to the 6th minute?",
    "choices": [
      "A. 0",
      "B. 1",
      "C. 2",
      "D. 3"
    ],
    "answer": "B",
    "type": "past",
    "question_level": "match",
    "related_event_index": [
      0
    ],
    "current_event_index": 0,
    "index": 1,
    "event_type": "corner"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team has taken more corners in the first half up to the 14th minute?",
    "choices": [
      "A. West Ham",
      "B. Chelsea",
      "C. Both teams have taken equal corners",
      "D. Neither team has taken a corner"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "past",
    "question_level": "team",
    "related_event_index": [
      0,
      1
    ],
    "current_event_index": 1,
    "index": 2,
    "event_type": "corner"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which player has taken the most corners in the first half up to the 20th minute?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Joao Mario",
      "B. Aaron Cresswell",
      "C. Willian",
      "D. Cesc Fabregas"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "past",
    "question_level": "player",
    "related_event_index": [
      0,
      1,
      2
    ],
    "current_event_index": 2,
    "index": 3,
    "event_type": "corner"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many total corners occurred in the first half?",
    "choices": [
      "A. 4",
      "B. 5",
      "C. 6",
      "D. 7"
    ],
    "answer": "D",
    "type": "half",
    "question_level": "match",
    "related_event_index": [
      0,
      1,
      2,
      3,
      4,
      5,
      6,
      8
    ],
    "current_event_index": null,
    "index": 4,
    "event_type": "corner"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team had the most corners in the first half?",
    "choices": [
      "A. West Ham",
      "B. Chelsea",
      "C. Both teams had equal corners",
      "D. Neither team had corners"
    ],
    "answer": "B",
    "type": "half",
    "question_level": "team",
    "related_event_index": [
      0,
      1,
      2,
      3,
      4,
      5,
      6,
      8
    ],
    "current_event_index": null,
    "index": 5,
    "event_type": "corner"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which player was involved in the most corners in the first half?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Joao Mario",
      "B. Aaron Cresswell",
      "C. Willian",
      "D. Cesc Fabregas"
    ],
    "answer": "B",
    "type": "half",
    "question_level": "player",
    "related_event_index": [
      0,
      1,
      2,
      3,
      4,
      5,
      6,
      8
    ],
    "current_event_index": null,
    "index": 6,
    "event_type": "corner"
  },
  {
    "question": "Will there be more corners in the first half after the 30th minute?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Yes",
      "B. No",
      "C. Only one more corner",
      "D. Two more corners"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "future",
    "question_level": "match",
    "related_event_index": [
      6,
      8
    ],
    "current_event_index": 5,
    "index": 7,
    "event_type": "corner"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team is more likely to get the next corner after the 25th minute?",
    "choices": [
      "A. West Ham",
      "B. Chelsea",
      "C. Both teams are equally likely",
      "D. Neither team will get another corner"
    ],
    "answer": "B",
    "type": "future",
    "question_level": "team",
    "related_event_index": [
      5,
      6,
      8
    ],
    "current_event_index": 4,
    "index": 8,
    "event_type": "corner"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which player is most likely to be involved in the next corner after the 35th minute?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Joao Mario",
      "B. Aaron Cresswell",
      "C. Willian",
      "D. Cesc Fabregas"
    ],
    "answer": "B",
    "type": "future",
    "question_level": "player",
    "related_event_index": [
      8
    ],
    "current_event_index": 6,
    "index": 9,
    "event_type": "corner"
  }
]